<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hosseinfeiz.com</title>
    <description>My personal Website for sharing my thoughts and works with rest of the world.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Useful Commands in Bash and Git </title>
        <description>
          Environment Variables In Scheduled Tasks - 
          ~&amp;gt; Get-Help -Name 'About_UsefulCommandsinBashandGit' This post covers a short story about why you shouldn't use profile related environment vars in scripts. Especially if you need to run them as scheduled tasks. | The Scenario I recently worked on a controller script to synchronize new active directory users with a two-factor...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-05-01-Bash/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-05-01-Bash/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What is the best way to learn Pytorch?</title>
        <description>
          ...made with include files and liquid tags - 
          I often start writing a post or page and end up with much more content than I thought at the beginning. So I started adding a little summary section like this: {: .text-muted} As mentioned earlier, I will post powershell and automation related stuff here. I've already started thinking about...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-04-07-PageSummary/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-04-07-PageSummary/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Latex for Thesis, Presentation and Reports</title>
        <description>
          
          ~&amp;gt; Get-Help -Name 'About_ThisPage' This post teachs you the basic commands that is needed for doing data science with command line. | &amp;nbsp;4&amp;nbsp;mins&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Hosseinfeiz General This blog is based on Dean`s jekyll theme beautiful-jekyll. Due to the requirements of the GDPR, I reworked some parts to ensure to be compliant. Because...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-03-09-Awk-Sed/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-03-09-Awk-Sed/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deep learning architectures</title>
        <description>
          
          I just started the resources page called A Journey to the PowerShell Citadel. It’s a maintained list of PowerShell resources split into 3 main parts / levels: Novice: Learn the most basic parts of powershell and know where to find the fundamental docs. Acolyte: Increase your knowledge in advanced topics...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-02-03-Deep-Learning-Using-Tensorflow/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-02-03-Deep-Learning-Using-Tensorflow/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The importance of VR</title>
        <description>
          Application of VR in Sport - 
          As mentioned earlier, I will post powershell and automation related stuff here. I’ve already started thinking about the following posts. Hosting a jekyll blog with incompatible plugins on Github.com While I created this blog I noticed that there are several plugins for jekyll which caused build errors on github. Yes...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2020-01-02-Hidden-markov-model/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2020-01-02-Hidden-markov-model/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Action Recognition</title>
        <description>
          A short story about how to create and use them. - 
          ~&amp;gt; Get-Help -Name 'About_ActionRecognition' This post is about preventing direct access to class properties with C# like getter and setter methods. It shows the syntax and usage of two different approaches. It ends with full github gist example you can work with in future. | Note: If you’re not familiar...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-11-19-NILM/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-11-19-NILM/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pose Estimation</title>
        <description>
          
          I’m thinking about starting a new series called The Debugger Tales. In this series I would like to share my experience in solving unique powershell problems. The problems itself will be practical examples which could appear in your daily business. With this knowledge you should easily avoid doing the same...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-10-24-Time-Series-Analysis/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-10-24-Time-Series-Analysis/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
